<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Siddhant Srivastav</title>
    <link>https://wickedbrat.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Siddhant Srivastav</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 09:19:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://wickedbrat.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The 3 life lessons</title>
      <link>https://wickedbrat.com/blog/the-3-life-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wickedbrat.com/blog/the-3-life-lessons/</guid>
      <description>When we talk about the one person whom I&amp;rsquo;d like to become, I find it really troubling to choose any one person. I&amp;rsquo;ve been really grateful to have met a lot of people who have taught me a great deal. My college seniors, my parents, my friends, some legends like Steve Jobs or even the fictional character Iron Man, they have all taught me one or more life changing lessons. But the one person who deserves the credit is my cousin brother, Adarsh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro to Actor Model</title>
      <link>https://wickedbrat.com/blog/intro-to-actor-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wickedbrat.com/blog/intro-to-actor-model/</guid>
      <description>Choosing the right system architecture to be used in production is one of the most important parts of the development process. It&amp;rsquo;s going to decide the reliability of the tech infrastructure in your organization. When running services at scale, things are often prone to break. Mostly not because one service runs faulty, but that one (or more) of them doesn&amp;rsquo;t let the other to work as expected. This calls for a need of architecture, some ground rules that solves these cases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with Clojure</title>
      <link>https://wickedbrat.com/blog/starting-with-clojure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wickedbrat.com/blog/starting-with-clojure/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re here, it means that probably you&amp;rsquo;ve come across functional programming or Clojure. If not, perhaps I need to check my SEO. Anyway, let&amp;rsquo;s make the most out of it. Throughout the blog, I&amp;rsquo;ll try to simplify and present my understanding of the Functional Programming and Clojure. When you&amp;rsquo;re getting started with Clojure, the book Brave Clojure is going to be your life saver. Joy of Clojure is another book you&amp;rsquo;d find handy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It all starts here</title>
      <link>https://wickedbrat.com/blog/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 09:19:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wickedbrat.com/blog/welcome/</guid>
      <description>It all starts here Hi fellow reader. Something tells me, you like reading for just plain-old checking out people&amp;rsquo;s profile? 😉 So before this blog, I&amp;rsquo;ve been writing at Medium.com . You can checkout whatever I&amp;rsquo;ve written here: Siddhant&amp;amp;rsquo; Profile . If there&amp;rsquo;s something you&amp;rsquo;d like to talk about, or would want to know my views on, click on any of the platforms below and ping me! Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to mention that you&amp;rsquo;re traveller from this website 😄</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>